<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shannon&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Shannon&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.136.4 &amp; FixIt v0.3.13</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 01:54:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On The Color Of The World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/0e4eb88/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 01:54:15 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/0e4eb88/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;April. 24th, 2023&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-the-color-of-the-world&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;On the Color of the World&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#on-the-color-of-the-world&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think, in many cases, that color is always so confusing. If it is because of personal experiences and other reasons that I choose to accept certain ideas and reject certain things. Then me, I&amp;rsquo;m always in denial. From the time I started making choices, I refused to accept them, but I was never able to reject the act of choosing itself. I could see my refusal quite clearly, but I was also refusing to accept my own disgusting refusal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The changes, always many, were great. Maybe something happened that caused some cracks to appear in my world. I used to doubt the real, the existential, because I was unwilling to accept that broken present world. I asked, how do I save you, how do I save you in this broken world, and the only response I got was silence. The only response I got was silence. So I started to think, starting with the activity of that childish thought, and I tried to discover the hue of that world. everything was so unreal. I remembered my memories, I remembered my experiences, I remembered the white brick walls, the green fake grass - they were just as vibrant in winter. Who was sharing with me in that empty world? Maybe I am overthinking, or maybe I am too selfish, and I am always unable to feel the truth of the Other, the emotions of the Other, the love of the Other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I choose to reject it? Is this my choice? Do I say that the colors of the world have fallen off so much because of my terrible trauma that I can no longer see all hope? Yet I want to see hope, and I always have hope. I say, why is it always me in my writing, why is it always myself in my thoughts. Did I ever make myself hard-hearted because I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to believe in my own weakness, or was it an attempt to escape from the colorful world?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Behold the colors of the world. Behold the sound of the world. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t see the world emerging, it&amp;rsquo;s my closure that prevents me from embracing it. Why? Why, to reject it? It is not that the world possesses a rift, but my heart possesses a rift. I am divided, and I myself cannot see my own most sincere words. Who else do you want to deceive? I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I can&amp;rsquo;t do it, I don&amp;rsquo;t have the capacity, I don&amp;rsquo;t have the ability to accept, to believe, to embrace. I say, it&amp;rsquo;s okay, I want you to live.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alive, what is it? Maybe just surviving, even if it&amp;rsquo;s under a dome of bleakness again. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not, I say. I say you can lose everything, you can lose everything you have, anything, but you have to have one thing. You must have it, a zest for life. It&amp;rsquo;s not a suggestion, it&amp;rsquo;s a requirement, a necessity. Rejection, coldness. Whatever word goes to describe it, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. Because the color of the world does not come from the world, I am the world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is easier said than done, and how difficult it is. I try everything, I try everything I can do. There is a limit to my power. I keep on, keep on, trying to find the answer in a higher body of knowledge. There is no answer. Perhaps colors do not hide themselves, or perhaps they have long since laid themselves bare in their most atrocious form. But what I see, I do not see them, I see myself. I see my dead body rotting in the fields. No! Don&amp;rsquo;t do this. I don&amp;rsquo;t want you to leave. But I&amp;rsquo;m sorry that I can never give you what you want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;O passionate life, it has never denied me. I just, can&amp;rsquo;t be near you. Why! Is it because I rejected it? Where exactly is the color, what exactly is it. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not, it&amp;rsquo;s not. I want everything of you. I want to be alive. The color did not fall off, the color never left me. And I have never rejected you, rejected your colors. Am I worthy? Do not ask questions! Do not doubt! Take action, take action! Passion is not some need, but a necessity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you pushing me? No, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, I regret saying that. Oh, the clouds, the clouds floating softly in the blue sky. What a beautiful day. So I stopped. The beauty of the world, I said, please stop for me. Not really asking for anything, but hoping that my passion, will save me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please, please, stop. Look at me, look into my eyes. I see, I see the real you. In your eyes, I see the colors of your heart. That splendid world is the very me that reflects everything. So, I stopped looking. Not because I found the answer, but because, on the contrary, there is no answer at all. Maybe the color of the world does not exist in the world. Perhaps, I can&amp;rsquo;t reject it either. I see its beauty. It was waiting for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strength, strength, I had an inexhaustible amount of energy in my body, but I swung my fist and punched the air. The bulge carried my body forward a ways. There was no crack, and if there was, why didn&amp;rsquo;t that punch hit the crack, why didn&amp;rsquo;t it reveal anything? Because I had become the whole of everything, the integration of everything. I stand in the world, and the world is my eye. So I see your determination, I see your courage, and your desire. Don&amp;rsquo;t compromise, don&amp;rsquo;t give up. You may remember the building, the friends there, the children there. No, I&amp;rsquo;m not for anyone. But I do understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The helplessness, the strength that has nowhere to use. Stop. Stop. I get it. You don&amp;rsquo;t. Are you just comforting me? No, I want you to have the most beautiful future. Can you see it? Can you see the patina in your heart? I wish you could see it too, I wish you had everything, everything you wanted. Because you have the passion, you always have it. So, I see it, the colors of the world.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sated Days Proposal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ec2641d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 01:42:01 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ec2641d/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/manifesto/">Manifesto</category>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Normandy Sherwood&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;APSS-UT 2&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 May 2022&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sated-days&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sated Days&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#sated-days&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I explained in an earlier article, modern men are dead. But how did they die? I have done a lot of theoretical analysis in the article, but I think the theory is not enough for people&amp;rsquo;s material life. As Karl Marx mentioned in his article &lt;em&gt;Theses On Feuerbach&lt;/em&gt;, &amp;ldquo;The philosophers have only interpreted the world, in various ways; the point is to change it.&amp;rdquo; I think my artistic creation is a practice of philosophical theory that changes the world. What I want to show is the process of a person dying. Not biological death, but internal, active, loss of the ability to live.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The artwork I want to make is a short film, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be the writer, director, and multiple handymen that don&amp;rsquo;t need to be subdivided. It focuses on the life of a delivery man. It tells the story of the protagonist from having a dream of changing the world, and then falling into a forbidden love. Then to sexual inversion, and disciplined cynics. Until the protagonist completely gave up all dreams and died. This may seem a bit abstract. If we describe it in a familiar way, it should be: an unemployed vagabond who dreams of a better life becomes a deliveryman and falls in love with a prostitute. Of course, as a lot of directors I love, they kill prostitutes, and of course I wanted to learn how by imitating. Following the story will continue: He brings food to her everyday, with his own coins. But in one day’s delivery, he finds abnormal screams and fighting noises comes out of her room. He dreams about being a hero and saves her, beats the bad guy, and free her from sex work. But he does nothing. He stands in front of the door, untill there is no sound inside. Then he leaves, while the murderer holds a knife looks at him from the peephole. Next day, the police calls him. Inform him that she is dead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea for this story took shape a long time ago. I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of the &lt;em&gt;Ghost in the Shell&lt;/em&gt; series, and I first got my hands on it about seven years ago. In its second TV series, &lt;em&gt;S.A.C. 2nd GIG&lt;/em&gt;, there is an episode titled &lt;em&gt;Night Cruise&lt;/em&gt;. In a cyberpunk world depicted by &lt;em&gt;Ghost in the Shell&lt;/em&gt;, portray the image of a driver. The refugee problem caused by the global local war, as well as the ethical problem in the context of prosthetic transformation - it happened that the driver had participated in the war at the same time and experienced full-body mechanization. He gradually felt that he was being cut out of society. He was dissatisfied with the work environment that was not respected by his boss, and fantasized about killing his boss by deliberately causing a car accident while driving (10:00-12:00). But he didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything, he just fantasized. I think I was deeply influenced by the work&amp;rsquo;s bold assumptions about world politics and the description of the existence of a highly developed capitalist society. Every small change in the world can be huge when projected on one of its people. I have to appreciate the influence &lt;em&gt;Ghost in the Shell&lt;/em&gt; had on my art style when I was younger.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The shattering of dreams, just like the trauma of falling into the Real Register after the shattering of Object a, is one of the processes in which modern people die. We constantly fantasize and then fall into but in such a postmodern society, all semiotic language has an overwhelming gravity. It forces us to face a world where desire is lost, and symbols are fragmented. How powerless we are in the face of it that we have to die. Until we get used to the feeling of surviving in chaos and can no longer be reborn. Poor sinking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Regarding the thinking behind this story, I think I myself am as sad as the protagonist. I am a Marxist artist, all my practice is an extension of the theory, and all my theories are for the people. Because practice is the only criterion for testing truth. But if there are people here who care as much as I do about the well-being of the people, the sad truth is that we have actually failed. The Left Revolution, like the delivery man, is alive but dead. Even so, should I do nothing? In fact, I did nothing. But I hate myself more for not being able to do anything. So I wanted to at least do something with this movie instead of sitting in a studio on top of an ivory tower and doing so-called art. I want to dedicate this film to all those who are fighting for the world, all who were, are, and will be fighting for a better tomorrow. All those who fight for freedom, equality. And the most important, for the people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How should we live? This is the only topic we can question now as dying people. What are we living for? Who do we work for? Does all the value we create belong to us? Modernity has killed us, and how? How should we live in this breathless world? I need to throw these questions through my artistic practice. I need to make people realize that we have to live!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But why, why is it necessary to express my arts to the people, and what is the importance of this work? It is truly a harsh question to answer: why we need to wake people up? I have not yet present a solution for the death of the leftist revolution yet, or to say, what shall we do to the modern society? I am in a cynics posture not pushing down the building, but it may not be a good choice to push it. There are people believing that they need a space in the building instead of pushing down the building. And my approach, is simply let us realize there are something we need to work on. There are people suffering. If we can see the truth of suffer, we can then practice the next step of pushing the building. Present them a life without the building is important. Reimagine a life outdoor is important. Democracy has to be built over the transparency of truth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how should it be done? Theories have limitations, especially in the face of what is happening. All I do is to express the information I think can be conveyed through artwork. Then the question will be starkly in front of us: how to push the building, and how do we survive after the building collapses? I would like to quote Slavoj Žižek, who once wrote in &lt;em&gt;The Parallax View&lt;/em&gt;, his most famous motto: &amp;ldquo;I would prefer not to&amp;rdquo;. I have always argued that we have to do something. But is my film, the artistic creation of all of us reduced to a force for strengthening what we are against? I think, I&amp;rsquo;m dead too, and I&amp;rsquo;m writing this in desperation. But at least, the dead deliveryman has to live, cynically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wish to publish this film onto the Internet. As how the Internet killed us, its influence of information will be part of my project’s ideal. But I do not expect any wave to be initiated. Not any fire to be started. I wish my starting point will motivate those who are practicing, and those who are realizing. I wish to show those fighters they are not alone, and meanwhile I will let more and more people to join our road toward a better future. The stage this will lead to, is a fire burning in the woods. Everything old will be destructed and a world born anew.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, remember to drink more water. As a process of existing, and an action that is actively perceiving exists. As a resistance to the potential death.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work Cited&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marx, Karl, and Frederick Engels. &lt;em&gt;Marx Engels - Selected Works Volume 1&lt;/em&gt;. First Edition, vol. 1, Foreign Languages Press, 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Production I.G. “Ghost in the Shell: Stand Alone Complex 2nd GIG Epi. 2.” &lt;em&gt;Dailymotion&lt;/em&gt;, uploaded by jenniferlinda9370, 2 Jan. 2019, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dailymotion.com/video/x6zvnr8&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.dailymotion.com/video/x6zvnr8&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ŽIžek, Slavoj. &lt;em&gt;The Parallax View (Short Circuits)&lt;/em&gt;. Reprint, The MIT Press, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thing We Lost in Modernity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/eeb197f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 01:29:09 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/eeb197f/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/research-paper/">Research Paper</category>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Normandy Sherwood&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;APSS-UT 2&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1 May 2022&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-thing-we-lost-in-modernity&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Thing We Lost in Modernity&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#the-thing-we-lost-in-modernity&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Franz Kafka was a German-language Bohemian novelist and short-story writer. His writing always presents a disgusting world where we feel be apart from ourselves - As how we feel in modern times.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In his work, &lt;em&gt;The Silence of the Sirens&lt;/em&gt;, he used five hundred words to tell a simple story: “To protect himself from the Sirens Ulysses stopped his ears with wax and had himself bound to the mast of his ship” (Kafka). When Ulysses traveled into the sea where the Sirens are, he heard nothing. He saw “their throats rising and falling, their breasts lifting, their eyes filled with tears, their lips half-parted”, and believed they are singing something. But sirens sang nothing, only silence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems like a simple story of Ulysses plugging his ears to prevent himself from being seduced by sirens. It&amp;rsquo;s just that Kafka has added a layer of skin to it, that is, sirens themselves do not sing. But this leads to another question that Kafka discussed in the last paragraph, that is, can Ulysses know that sirens didn&amp;rsquo;t sing, or did he start thinking about the possibility that sirens didn&amp;rsquo;t sing? This is a bold rewrite of the story in Homer&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;The Odyssey&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Specifically, what Kafka expresses is actually what Ulysses loses in rejection. In the story, Ulysses can no longer prove that sirens didn&amp;rsquo;t sing. If we make a bolder generalization, we should say that modern people are Ulysses. We all lose something in rejection. The sirens-like silence conveyed by Kafka is, instead, a powerful resistance. But before resisting, we should see Ulysses&amp;rsquo; rejection, and his cynicism disciplined by modernity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The so-called modernity refers to a structure under the discourse of modern society. For example, the life of modern people cannot be separated from the construction of factories, currencies, the Internet, and other infrastructure. Strictly speaking, modernity does not have such a concrete representation of reality. However, the social phenomenon manifested by modern life itself has modernity. If we look at another dimension of modern life, the most appropriate example should be the Internet. Specifically, it should be a semiotic transmission mode under the discourse power of capitalism - but modernity does not only exist in capitalism, what is emphasized here is the modernity constructed by the capitalist discourse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since smartphones and the Internet entered millions of households ten years ago, there has been a scary social phenomenon: people seem to have gradually lost their ability to criticize, or the question of if people lost their ability to think under the influence of big data is being more and more asked. So, what exactly is modernity? What kind of predicament have people stepped into under the discipline of modernity? Let’s start with the conclusion: Modern men are dead. Modern men have lost the ability to perceive and reflect, so we are dead. We can no longer cause any substantial disruption to any existing architecture, but simply go with the flow. We are no longer part of history, but modern data at the end of history. How so? How do modern people die? We need to start with how modernity affects people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modernity is a dissolution of tradition, which can lead to a terrifying sense of rupture. Because when people no longer have the ability to perceive tradition or pre-modernity. Modernity has become the only tradition. Traditional traditions are dismantled and replaced by unconventional traditions. From Michel Foucault&amp;rsquo;s point of view, modernity is the process of rule building, which imbues life with unconventional order and procedures. Michel Foucault is a representative of 20th-century French philosophy, and his research on power and the control of modernity is collected in his book &lt;em&gt;Discipline and Punish&lt;/em&gt;. Foucault mainly discusses how the prison - as an object of modernity&amp;rsquo;s mode of punishment - came into being. The death of modern people is carried out in prisons, but not a physical one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He found prison in many cases valuable as a vehicle for punishment because it is a space. However, precisely because it is a space, the discipline of the prison does not appear to be universal. If a prison requires space to function, then it is not universal, not ultimately economic. The real prison should be the discipline of power itself. Something unseen. “The general juridical form that guaranteed a system of rights that were egalitarian in principle was supported by these tiny, everyday, physical mechanisms, by all those systems of micro-power that are essentially non-egalitarian and asymmetrical that we call the disciplines” (Foucault 222). As Foucault states in his essay, in this type of power, the severity of the punishment itself is of secondary importance, or even whether it occurs in reality or not. The key is to make people think that it is ubiquitous and instill a set of political and moral education requirements and norms that it carries into every citizen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Foucault called the prison the Panopticon, which was proposed by another English philosopher, Jeremy Bentham, in a 1791 letter titled &lt;em&gt;Panopticon, or The Inspection House&lt;/em&gt;. This new, modern prison consists of a small shutter on each cell door so that prisoners cannot see outside clearly. And in the center of the prison, there is a tower where the guards can see everyone into any cells - even if they&amp;rsquo;re not actually looking at a particular prisoner, the prisoners imagine the guards are looking at them. The purpose of the Panopticon is to complete a process of internalization through a series of representations and spectacles. Furthermore, symbolic power constructs an imaginary world of meaning-giving; in this world, a variety of symbols, discourses, and meanings circulate. And our identity construction is entirely dependent on the unilateral indoctrination and reeducation of this symbolic world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the subject of discipline in modern society is not an individual or a group, but a virtual reality. What virtual reality stands for here is not technological, a virtual space that can be seen, created by a display screen. It is because it is invisible in itself, but it has indeed become part of the construction of society. Contrasted with Foucault&amp;rsquo;s prisons, the problem with modern life is that we actually live in prisons. This prison should be called big data. The term big data does not simply refer to a certain way of data collection and processing, but to the way humans exist in the entire networked society. The virtual becomes reality, and this is the problem we face.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since the birth of online social media, all kinds of &amp;ldquo;Sock Puppets&amp;rdquo; have been created continuously. This &amp;ldquo;Sock Puppet&amp;rdquo; is a transcendental rule constructed by virtual reality, that is, the subject of discipline. In modern social life, the most appropriate example should be &amp;ldquo;credit card&amp;rdquo;. A credit card has a nature: it can be lost or stolen. When a similar situation occurs, the purchases made by the credit card during the period of loss will be considered as actual purchases by the holder. Credit cards go beyond virtual reality. It&amp;rsquo;s not the cardholder, but it goes beyond the cardholder. It can fully represent the holder without the holder&amp;rsquo;s presence. In other words, even if the holder is standing there, the individual still has to stand a &amp;ldquo;Sock Puppet&amp;rdquo; in front of him to represent himself, so that this person can be accepted by the modern system and can join the social group that has been disciplined by modernity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like a Panopticon-type prison, the identity of the modern man is no longer defined by the man himself but has become a symbol defined by the process of indoctrination. In the modern network society, the footprints left by each person in the network are intertwined and become the label for the network to identify the individual. This label is actually more powerful than the person because it transcends the individual it originally represents. What this label represents is the negation of the self who is more like the self than the self, but they are the same inside, because they are all the self, but at the same time they are the negation of the self that is beyond the self.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This leads to a problem, that is, modern people have lost the ability to identify themselves. Because they themselves can no longer represent themselves. They were surpassed. This is a real phenomenon, not an inference. The reason for this phenomenon is that the network itself cannot represent anyone. It is not trustworthy in itself but is given by all who trust it. However, once this trust structure is established, the person who gives it trust is no longer trustworthy. Because there is already a more authoritative and credible discipline subject. And, under this norm, the discipline subject will consolidate its authority step by step. And this method is personalized recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personalized recommendation refers to a modern contact that is completely opposite to the traditional way of contacting information. For example, propaganda is a recommendation, but not personalized. Personalized recommendations are a kind of fertile nourishment that is integral to the modern transparent prison. It is a kind of absolute unfreedom that allows individuals to self-discipline in an attitude of absolute freedom. Take any social media or video platform as an example, their &amp;ldquo;trend&amp;rdquo; is a personalized recommendation. &amp;ldquo;Trend&amp;rdquo; usually suggests content that users may be interested in based on their browsing history: the results produced by this algorithm are usually generated by comparing with other users who have also viewed the overlapping contents. It presents content that people are likely to like in a smart way, not content that disagrees with them. On the surface, users have absolute freedom of choice: they can freely choose among the nearly infinite contents derived from personalized recommendations, but in fact these choices are not free in nature. They are personalized.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through personalized recommendations, big data can further understand individual tendencies and further represent individual choices. And where it will end up, is the individuation of an individual who has lost the ability to choose. In the step-by-step process of dismantling the individual, what we can foresee is the rejection of modern people—the Ulysses-style rejection. As with the working model of &amp;ldquo;trend&amp;rdquo;, once it gives people certain choices, people reject other choices that are not those.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rejection is the absence of the ability to choose. Rejection in this context is a complete loss of the possibility to see the negativity of permission—as big data is supposed to work. Ulysses refused to hear the silence of sirens, thinking that his choice was free. But in reality, he was completely unfree. He was disciplined in a prostrate posture: the belief that refusal to hear is an acceptance. This is an obedience. For us, this reality leads to another problem. That is the price of obedience. This can be further diverged by a theory on interrogation that Foucault cites at the end of the book.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Foucault ends the book with a discussion of the role of interrogation in the criminal justice system. The interrogation will continue to find reasons for criminals&amp;rsquo; behavior from the life and behavior of the prisoner, that is, the prisoner becomes a prisoner is not accidental, but inevitable. The interrogation will focus on &amp;ldquo;Why did you become such a person?&amp;rdquo; Such questioning leads to the fact that in the end, even the prisoner himself will feel that he must become a prisoner. This makes it extremely difficult for prisoners to reintegrate into society. Prisons treat them as a resource that can be managed by keeping them on the fringes of society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Stranger&lt;/em&gt; by Albert Camus is a short novel. Albert Camus was a French philosopher, author, and journalist, and the winner of the 1957 Nobel Prize in Literature. The novel is based on the death of the protagonist Meursault&amp;rsquo;s mother. Meursault did not grieve after the death of his mother, but was rather indifferent, even dating a new girlfriend the day after his mother was buried. However, Meursault did not expect that his behavior was not understood by everyone, so after he accidentally killed his friend&amp;rsquo;s opponent, he was accused by everyone that he had no feelings for his mother and was a born villain, then was finally sentenced to death. Meursault&amp;rsquo;s actions are not actually inhuman, but simply absurd, according to Camus. Meursault is looking at the world from a nihilistic point of view as if he has maintained a huge sense of distance from everything that is happening around him, and everything has lost its meaning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During Meursault&amp;rsquo;s interrogation, the judge repeatedly asked the question he had already asked, &amp;ldquo;he asked if I loved Maman&amp;rdquo; (Camus 67). The judge asked if he loved his mother, and what he was thinking when he pulled the trigger to kill the victim. Meursault seemed calm and even a little apathetic to the repeated questioning as if he was unconsciously saying that he loved his mother and that he shot somebody because the sand was red, and the sun was hot. Like Foucault&amp;rsquo;s analysis of the interrogation, the judge&amp;rsquo;s questioning is to prove that Meursault should be a villain and to convince himself that he is a villain. The judge found that Meursault had no remorse at all but that Meursault simply felt he was telling the truth. The discipline of the court was to make Meursault a villain and to make him believe he is a villain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like the title of Camus&amp;rsquo; book, &lt;em&gt;The Stranger&lt;/em&gt;, Meursault became a socially marginalized stranger. One has to prove that he is a human being to return to the acceptance of society. But this begs the dreaded question, will &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo; be a stranger? Meursault was charged with murder, but the judge needed to know why he didn&amp;rsquo;t cry at his mum&amp;rsquo;s funeral. Because this behavior is not human or does not obey the symbolic discipline of society. If this proposition is pushed to the limit, anyone may be a disobedient person, and anyone may be sentenced to extreme punishment for this. When everyone is laughing, if a person is crying, that individual becomes a strange person, regardless of whether the person actually wants to cry. What&amp;rsquo;s more terrifying is that the crying person will also think that self is abnormal, and thus lose the ability to think about discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this way, the discipline of modernity makes people completely immersed in a society full of symbolic discipline. And believing that they should be in the right place as much as surrendering. Virtual reality, and the Sock Puppet performed in it, have forced modern humans to identify themselves by simulacrums. By looking at the screen - not the mirror - the virtual world we see is becoming reality. Step by step, they occupy the real space that should belong to us by representing us. The problem with these virtual things is not that they are too virtual, but that they are not virtual enough. &lt;em&gt;Needy Girl Overdose&lt;/em&gt; is a GalGame released in early 2022. The whole game is based on a premise: hate the Internet, but can&amp;rsquo;t live without it. I want to be praised by everyone, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be in contact with real people. This is clearly divisive. Ame-chan is the main character in the game who has a conversation with the player. She is a mentally ill, impoverished girl. She dropped out of school at home, and the player, as her boyfriend and producer, helped her become a popular streamer. In order to pay the rent and to meet the need to be noticed, Ame put on a wig, put on heavy makeup, and interacted with the live audience on the Internet. In this case, KAngel, Ame&amp;rsquo;s webcast image, is her &amp;ldquo;credit card&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The game has a variety of endings, and Ame will also get different experiences and endings according to the different options players choose during the game. Ame could graduate—retire from her streamer industry, fall in love with players, or break up. One of the endings, titled &lt;em&gt;There Are No Angels&lt;/em&gt;, was caused by not getting enough fans for Ame in a long time. In that ending, Ame stayed below five hundred thousand subscribers for thirty days, so she jumped off the ground and left the world. In the end, the last text on the screen is: &amp;ldquo;Love and online numbers are her coping mechanisms.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The problem with the Internet isn&amp;rsquo;t that it&amp;rsquo;s too virtual, it&amp;rsquo;s that it&amp;rsquo;s not virtual enough. When people pay too much attention to the virtual symbolic world or are immersed in the symbolic discipline of society, they lose the ability to perceive reality in the sense of distance. Virtual reality, as a non-reality that is not virtual enough, is a constant, painful, and traumatic questioning of people trying to escape discipline. People lose themselves in discipline and lose their ability to maintain themselves in the process of trying to find themselves. To borrow Debord&amp;rsquo;s concept, we are all spectacles. Guy-Ernest Debord was a French Marxist theorist, philosopher, and filmmaker. In his book &lt;em&gt;The Society of the Spectacle&lt;/em&gt;, he believed in analyzing the media, or how propaganda killed modern men is the core of modernity analysis. A fundamental concept in the book, &amp;ldquo;spectacle&amp;rdquo;, is constantly changing, sometimes as images, but sometimes as commodities, social relations, organizations, or worldviews. The spectacle doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be a specific concept of matter. Strictly speaking, the spectacle is a constitutive principle of a highly media-developed society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spectacle, similar to an exhibition. Put something in a glass case on the street for the public to see. And its purpose is to let people enter the system represented by the spectacle. Ame&amp;rsquo;s behavior, being a streamer, is essentially that she wants to be popular. In the process, she inevitably symbolizes and commodifies herself. Ame put herself in the exhibition cabinet called the live broadcast room, doing her best to improve her semiotic value. Landscape yourself, turn yourself into a pure symbol. Debord&amp;rsquo;s spectacle theory is based on the analysis of consumerism. Basically, Debord argues, the purpose of spectacles is consumption, and consumerism in turn commodifies our lives. In the process, our desires are dissipated: because everything can be bought - even if it is not. It also makes people think we need more, not want more. And the fundamental driving force is vanity and narcissism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The concept of the disappearance of desire complements the theory of virtual reality above in a different way. Because virtual reality serves a consumerist society, as in Ame&amp;rsquo;s case, her virtual life is a resource for real life. And the spectacle is also virtual, it separates everything from reality and drags it into the theatre of the spectacle. All the real things have become imaginary, all the real things are cosplaying, and they are all symbolized and commercialized. Instead, everything that is virtual is becoming reality. Instead of reading, we buy books and put them on display on the living room shelf. We spend in coffee shops and use every purchase to contribute to a fund for third-world children. Even life ceases to be life, it becomes a pure sign, a spectacle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have lost our ability to see true purity in a purely symbolic order. The desire for modern life is occupied by consumerism, and the desire itself is eliminated. And virtual reality is eating away at the rest. We end up in total rejection of reality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What was lost, as Ulysses did, was the ability to imagine different possibilities. And this dissolution is produced through the construction of modernity power. Reality is disappearing and we reject reality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the order of modernity, people are lost. And specifically, they lost the ability to think under the mandate of technology and consumerism. What is lost is the ability to reflect on whether they have been disciplined or not. Or, to think about whether sirens are singing. This dissolution takes place through ideological discipline. The way of discipline is through the absence of choice, or, in other words, the absence of possibility. What we actually lose is the ability to know that things might be different. Like Ulysses, we plug our ears, lose our hearing, and lose the possibility of resistance. Because we can no longer know whether it is possible for sirens to be silent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, modern men are dead. Not because of our physical flaws, but because we live in a breeding ground of over-completeness. This swaddling warmth makes us reluctant to face the suffering that is happening. This is the refusal under the discipline of modernity. When we reject it completely, we die. We die in prison: a fully symbolic virtual reality, a breathless spectacle society filled with meaning and ideology. We cosplay behind the credit card, and commodify ourselves into spectacles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, in such a situation, what should we do? What should our life be like? Does it have to be dry firewood to be burned? The resistance of sirens was silence. But why does it have to be silence? Or fundamentally, is the silence of sirens resisting, what are sirens doing? There is a chasm between speech and silence, this chasm is absence. But silence is not nothing. Silence expresses another mode of speech, speech that lacks content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before silence, it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to go back to &lt;em&gt;The Stranger&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;s text. Meursault in the book cares nothing, the world has no meaning. But from what Camus wanted to convey, he was not an absurd, irrational person. On the contrary, he is a sun-loving man with a passion for life. Everything he does seems so absurd, so socially disjointed. Meursault&amp;rsquo;s approach is a rejection of discipline. He loves being and feeling itself, not value judgments. The judge&amp;rsquo;s interrogation was aimed at getting Meursault to admit that he did regret the death of his mother and the death of the victim. But he does not think he is regretful, and even firmly believes that he is happy. He refuses to accept value judgments, and his nihilistic vision sees everything as equal. Nothing is worth more than another. Precisely because he rejected the constraints of society, he did not lie in court. He said the motivation for the killing was that the sun was hot because he did feel the sun was hot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this sense, he is a stranger. Because he stood by his own truth. But is truth itself a value judgment? Isn&amp;rsquo;t that the norm of that kind of society? On the contrary, there is no universal thing or reason that tries to convince others. It is a complete revelation of the contingency and absurdity of existence. Because, as Meursault thought, the world is absurd and meaningless. In fact, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t care how things are, because things exist in and of themselves. How things are is not a thought, but a reality. Meursault&amp;rsquo;s truth is truth precisely because it has no meaning and therefore no room for refutation. He lives in purity that has taken off the cloak of semiotics. He stared straight at the hot, full, shadowless sun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meursault is powerless. He has no power to overturn the existing order - like all disciplined modern people. Or to him, even doing so would be meaningless. In fact, his incompetence made him the most powerful force. Like the silence of the sirens, they were powerless in the face of the Ulysses who rejected them completely. However, their incompetence made them choose silence. Silence instead became the most powerful weapon against Ulysses. The only way to really get Ulysses to accept it is to make him wonder if sirens actually sing. Silence adds meaning to this choice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For none of us has said anything, but in the absence of meaning all semiotic speech is encompassed, but at the same time, all is sublated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or is that a practical solution?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work Cited&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bentham, Jeremy. &lt;em&gt;Panopticon: Or The Inspection House (1791)&lt;/em&gt;. Kessinger Publishing, LLC, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Camus, Albert, and Matthew Ward. &lt;em&gt;The Stranger&lt;/em&gt;. Vintage, 1989.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Debord, Guy. &lt;em&gt;Society Of The Spectacle&lt;/em&gt;. Black and Red, 2002.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fisher, Marc. “Flushing out the True Cause of the Global Toilet Paper Shortage amid Coronavirus Pandemic.” &lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, 7 Apr. 2020, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/coronavirus-toilet-paper-shortage-panic/2020/04/07/1fd30e92-75b5-11ea-87da-77a8136c1a6d_story.html&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.washingtonpost.com/national/coronavirus-toilet-paper-shortage-panic/2020/04/07/1fd30e92-75b5-11ea-87da-77a8136c1a6d_story.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Foucault, Michel, and Alan Sheridan. &lt;em&gt;Discipline and Punish: The Birth of the Prison&lt;/em&gt;. Vintage Books, 1995.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Homer, and Emily Wilson. &lt;em&gt;The Odyssey&lt;/em&gt;. 1st Edition, W. W. Norton and Company, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kafka, Franz, and Edwin Muir, translators. &lt;em&gt;The Silence of the Sirens&lt;/em&gt;. Martin Secker, 1933.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Needy Girl Overdose.&lt;/em&gt; Xemono Co., Ltd, 2022&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unfinished Dreams of Kon Satoshi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/3063866/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 00:51:41 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/3063866/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/research-paper/">Research Paper</category>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Normandy Sherwood&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ASPP-UT 2&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;8 Mar. 2022&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-unfinished-dreams-of-kon-satoshi&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Unfinished Dreams of Kon Satoshi&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#the-unfinished-dreams-of-kon-satoshi&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“With my heart full of gratitude for everything good in the world, I&amp;rsquo;ll put down my pen. Now excuse me, I have to go” (Kon). These were the last words Kon Satoshi wrote on his deathbed. In May 2010, he went to the hospital due to physical discomfort and was found to have pancreatic cancer. In August of the same year, Kon Satoshi passed away at the age of 46 (Loo). He is a famous Japanese animation director who only directed six works in his lifetime. The last work &lt;em&gt;Dream Machine&lt;/em&gt; was never finished because of his death. As he said in his last words, he always respects his artistic process and appreciates the team that helped him. He regrets that he can no longer finish work that was halfway done. Although the number of works is not large, he has truly achieved that every film is a rich stroke in film history. Each of his works has won many international awards and has been studied and imitated by later directors of various countries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Different from Miyazaki&amp;rsquo;s warmth and Shinkai&amp;rsquo;s freshness, Kon Satoshi is keen to describe the pressures faced by urbanites in modern society and explore the connection between reality and fantasy. The plots of his films are is mostly based on dreams. Imaginative fantasy, magical editing, and nuanced details constitute his unforgettable personal style. Watching his films often brings a unique experience of wandering between reality and the dream. Kon Satoshi is a dream maker, as Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s autobiography &lt;em&gt;Kon&amp;rsquo;s Tone&lt;/em&gt; described himself. One of Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s most magnificent works, &lt;em&gt;Paprika&lt;/em&gt;, also talks about &amp;ldquo;dream&amp;rdquo; directly from &amp;ldquo;dream&amp;rdquo;. So, there is nothing wrong with interpreting Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s creations from a dream perspective.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Perfect Blue&lt;/em&gt; is the first film directed by Kon Satoshi. To most people, this is not only Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s debut work but a work that establishes his style and shows his genius. It can be said that the debut is the peak. The film is a story about the transformation of an idol singer into an actor. The protagonist, Mima, is a member of a J-pop group. She leaves the group and becomes an actress. But not all her fans are happy with this decision, which caused her to be being threatened and tracked by some crazy fans. After shooting a scene that Mima plays as a victim of rape, she becomes jumpy and can no longer distinguish reality and her actress life. Which is a sign of dissociative disorder. And after she becomes psycho, most of the actors, cameramen, writers in the rape scene get murdered. In fact, it is her agent, an actress who once failed, who is jealous of her beauty and success and wants to become Mima. That is the reason the agent killed the actors who raped Mima in the film. &lt;em&gt;Perfect Blue&lt;/em&gt; is an animated film that combines suspense, thriller, and fantasy. The atmosphere of suspense and horror haunts the mind all the time, making the audience unable to guess what will happen in the next second, and can only get increasingly into it. The climax and the ending are even more striking. Fantasy and reality are depicted so close to each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Perfect Blue&lt;/em&gt; is a film about anxiety. Mima starts her collapse from the first time she left her comfort zone. The path of an actress is unknown and fully covered under the shadow. The pressure of the new job, questions, and disappointment of her fans, creates anxiety. Moreover, being an idol is an exposure of her personal. While the story happens in the age when the Internet just spread out, televisions, cameras, websites are all the extensions of the eyes. Therefore, Mima’s life is under Gaze. The relation between lookers and being looked at is multidimensional. Because not only her fans are looking, her movie fans, collaborators, everyone who pays attention to her, and even us, the audience of the movie &lt;em&gt;Perfect Blue&lt;/em&gt;, have become her lookers. Mima is being placed under spotlights and cameras, under Gaze. These Gazes are the reason for anxiety, which is a feeling of unpleasure, danger. Anxiety is a lack of something, as Jacques Lacan, a French psychoanalyst described: &amp;ldquo;Anxiety, as we know, is always connected with a loss……with a two-sided relation on the point of fading away to be superseded by something else, something which the patient cannot face without vertigo&amp;rdquo; (Lacan 273). Anxiety is a potential loss, which is an expectant dread. The fear of losing something in the expectation, which has not yet come true. In the case of Mima, the expectation is what she imagines others want her to be. Her agent wants her to be an actor, her fans want her to go back to be a singer. She does not know which is the best choice for them, but those are what she imagines they want her to be. She does not know if they will be satisfied in any situation. As Lacan said in his &lt;em&gt;Seminar IX&lt;/em&gt;, &amp;ldquo;……anxiety is the sensation of the desire of the Other&amp;rdquo; (Lacan). Take a deeper look into Mima’s case, what she is facing is a concealed object of desire: the crazy fan. A crazy fan is a man who acts like a stalker. He is a Gazer yet hidden behind a curtain. Mima is not able to find him, but the existence of this stalker still creates a Gaze. In the process of generating anxiety, there must be an Other that the sensation is imagining. But now the stalker is in the darkness where Mima cannot see. Then the anxiety becomes even more because the target of sensation is lacking now. The Other is missing, but it is there. This unknown Other creates more options for suspicion, which leads to larger anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon Satoshi’s works focus on dreams, as Mima’s sensation of the unknown. The expectation is another form of a dream. Imagining what is possible is common throughout the sensation and expectation. Desire is another key term in his film. Another work &lt;em&gt;Millennium Actress&lt;/em&gt; is an animated film, it is about an interview with an actor Chiyoko who is now retired and aged. The film focuses on the life and experience of Chiyoko from her childhood to her end of being an actor. At an immature age in middle school, she met a painter who is listed as wanted. She helped the painter to hide from the polices, and the painter gave her a key to thank her. She found herself in love with the painter, but the next morning, the painter is gone. The technique of storytelling in this film is a masterpiece, this film is well known for its title of “textbook of montage.” During the interview, the interviewers are interacting with Chiyoko and make the story structure messy and unrealistic. The interviewers join the recall of Chiyoko and become part of her memory. She starts to become an actor because she thinks that thought if she is famous, the painter will find her again. While Chiyoko is recalling her life, her experience as an actor and her seeking for the painter interweaves together into a dreamy story which let the audience unable to configure if the scene is she acting in the film or is her real life. At the end of the film, the director created an eight-minute-long montage, which became a legend in film history.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chiyoko loves the painter. Her entire life as an actor is the process of finding the painter, and the reason she is so successful is that she puts her real emotion of demanding the painter into her acting. In her acting career, the person she loves in the film is not another actor’s character, but the painter. Even the painter never comes to find her, Chiyoko always believes that the painter is somewhere. Painter, in this case, is Chiyoko’s desire, but it is not something fixed, it is an Object a. “In Lacan&amp;rsquo;s seminars of the late 1950s and early 1960s, the evolving concept of the object (petit) a is viewed in the matheme of phantasy as the object of desire sought in the other&amp;hellip;a deliberate departure from British Object Relations psychoanalysis” (Mary 26). In &lt;em&gt;Perfect Blue&lt;/em&gt;, Mima’s anxiety is caused by the sensation of the desire of the Other. And the object that caused anxiety is Object a. It is also the object of desire. In the film &lt;em&gt;Millennium Actress&lt;/em&gt;, Chiyoko wants to find the painter, the painter, in this case, is Chiyoko’s Object a. Object a is the fragments of the Real register. The Real register, according to Lacan, is firstly is a prelinguistic unspeakable world. Humans enter the Symbolic register through language, but the Real register is not possible to be fully symbolized, there must be something remaining. This remnant is Object a, it marks a location in the Real register where language is faulty. Language exposes its inconsistency. The symbolic movement must have a remnant. The painter Chiyoko wants to find is not there yet, but Chiyoko believes that there is a painter. She symbolized the sign of the painter into a Symbolic register, and the rest of what is not symbolic becomes the Object a.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this case, Chiyoko expresses her desire to the painter in her acting, but in films she acts, there is no painter. The painter becomes a symbol of the painter, but no longer the real painter. However, in Chiyoko’s desire, she believes there is a painter, there must be. This painter is the remnant of symbolization. That is the object of desire, a frame of fantasy. Chiyoko pretends that the character she acts to love in the films is the real painter, thus, she connects the Real register and the Symbolic register together by dreaming about the painter. Dreaming about the painter makes Chiyoko away from knowing if the painter is still alive. This little bite of finding the unreal painter is a Jouissance, which is, pleasure. Chiyoko touches this Jouissance by attempting to get to her Object a, but the precondition is, the painter is alive. The death of the painter is the most brilliant design in the story of this film. Later when Chiyoko becomes a successful actor and gets married to a director that loves her, she found herself still searching for the painter. But now she is a wife, she is no longer suitable to love another man. And this is when she gets to know that the painter is dead even before she became an actor. After she got married and before she knows the painter is dead, she believes that the painter is the one who can bring her Jouissance since she found herself is trapped in a marriage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Death breaks everything. Chiyoko’s Object a collapsed after she knows that the painter is dead. This de-symbolized the painter and makes the Object a collapse into the Real register. This traumatic experience required a compensatory pleasure to fulfill. If Chiyoko chooses to hide the trauma with compensatory pleasure, then she will need another Object a as a frame of fantasy to reach the pleasure, which caused the desire continuous infinitely. Because if this Object a collapses again, the cycle will continue. It is necessary to traverse the fantasy. Chiyoko understood there is nothing as a painter, the Object a is not in the Real register but only fragments. The painter is not there. Or to say, the painter as a symbol is not the painter himself, the painter in Chiyoko’s mind is not the real painter. Even say, there is nothing beyond fantasy, there will be nothing after she traverses the fantasy. But to emphasize, fantasy is a form of desire, not the object of desire. In Chiyoko’s case, the painter is the Object a, and her love for the painter is the fantasy that pushes her to find him. “To traverse the fantasy, Lacan theorizes, is to cease positing that the Other has taken the ‘lost’ object of desire. It is to accept that this object is something posited by oneself to compensate for the experienced trauma of castration” (Sharpe). And Chiyoko succeeds at the end of her life. The film ends with a scene when the old Chiyoko lays over the bed in a hospital, the film cuts into a scene that young Chiyoko is laying in a rocket to space. Her words are: “After all, what I really love is the pursuit of him” (&lt;em&gt;Millennium Actress&lt;/em&gt; 1:22:00). She accepts that there is no Object a that can satisfy her. There is no something superior. Fantasy is constructed by the subject’s desire. After she realized that the fantasy is constructed by her subjectivity, she found her fundamental fantasy, which is that she is the one who can construct the positivity that supports her to the end of her actor life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As above, the ontological reflections that Kon Satoshi includes in his films are philosophically profound. When audiences watch his films, they are not only learning about the story, but empathizing with the story as a projection of themselves. This unique narrative connects Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s films with the audience in the dimension of the fourth wall.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The characteristics of Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s later narrative style are always focusing on the stories of a heroine, the confrontational power of the alien world, the reaction of each character, and each dramatic conflict. It all revolves around this heroine, in his work &lt;em&gt;Paranoia Agent&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Millennium Actress&lt;/em&gt; all shows this heroine style. This heroine is small and broad, and the story will be full of tension and absurdity, but it makes sense. Using subconscious descriptions, vague fantasy, and the distance from reality, to show the changes in the character&amp;rsquo;s heart. In Kon Satoshi’s film, his heroines are always suffering under a certain emotion. From all the analyses above, it is distinct that his characters are driven by their inner emotions instead of pushing by the plot. This storytelling that is character driven is extremely fascinating combine with Kon Satoshi’s editing style. He succeeds in presenting a character that is so similar to a real person who can be psychoanalyzed precisely. This realistic style in character rendition is influenced heavily by his early animation experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro Otomo is Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s teacher. In other words, when Kon Satoshi had not yet become a director in his early years, Kon Satoshi first participated in the film directed by Katsuhiro Otomo. The style of Katsuhiro Otomo&amp;rsquo;s creation is like the waves of the ocean, with undercurrents surging. So, Katsuhiro Otomo often takes the fate of humankind as the theme, reflecting on the relationship between human achievements and human beings themselves. He will discuss mostly topics like &amp;ldquo;Technology and power will eventually bring destruction.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro Otomo is particularly interested in &amp;ldquo;Destruction&amp;rdquo;. In the movie &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt;, Tokyo was destroyed twice, the world war was once, and the Akira energy rampage was once again. Since then, disaster scenes of &amp;ldquo;destruction&amp;rdquo; are common in his screenwriter and director&amp;rsquo;s works: the runaway elderly care machine in &lt;em&gt;Old Man Z&lt;/em&gt; continuously absorbs and combines, and finally becomes a mechanical monster; in &lt;em&gt;Metropolis&lt;/em&gt;, the robot heroine incarnates as a human weapon; In &lt;em&gt;Steamboy&lt;/em&gt;, the steam city is finally destroyed. In short, the end of the movie must be &amp;ldquo;destroy the world&amp;rdquo;, and the depiction of disaster scenes increases the number of paintings and the workload of storytelling and leads to high production costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The root of the disaster is the misuse of technology. Katsuhiro Otomo&amp;rsquo;s work has a keen sense of &amp;ldquo;didactic&amp;rdquo;, which is derived from this. This is a recurring theme in his work. Katsuhiro Otomo&amp;rsquo;s attitude towards technology is overly complicated. On the one hand, he describes the impact of advanced technology on the world in his animation, which brings convenience to human beings; on the other hand, the story often ends with the negative effects of technology. From this perspective, Katsuhiro Otomo is quite vigilant about technology. Katsuhiro Otomo describes technology as a potential threat that might cause destruction. Kon Satoshi brings the idea of destruction into his work as a factor of suffering. In Kon Satoshi’s story, the protagonists are always unfree, they are suffering under a certain emotion. Compare to Katsuhiro Otomo’s direct showing the destructing city in screen, Kon Satoshi is focused on a slower destruction, a hardship in person.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro Otomo uses a rich and varied visual language in the film to highlight the contradiction between modern technology and human development - human beings will be backed up by the technological achievements they admire at any time. In addition, Katsuhiro Otomo also integrates Hollywood movies and cyberpunk culture to make a real wish for the social characteristics of the Japanese and promote the development of sci-fi realism animation to the peak.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro Otomo is meticulous about the performance of the realism of the picture. His pursuit of authenticity made the reflections on the glass of the building in &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; optically accurate. The richness and precision of detail in any one image change the style of Kon Satoshi with whom he works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon Satoshi participated in the scripting of the first short film &lt;em&gt;Her Memory&lt;/em&gt; in the animated short series &lt;em&gt;Memorizu&lt;/em&gt; that Katsuhiro Otomo oversaw. Kon Satoshi also condenses his understanding of dreams, virtuality, and reality into this short thirty minutes. In it, Katsuhiro Otomo&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of truth has influenced Kon Satoshi deeply. But Kon Satoshi fuses real visuals with his peculiar penchant for &amp;ldquo;dreamland&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s work has influenced directors better known than him, such as Christopher Nolan and Darren Aronofsky. Christopher Nolan&amp;rsquo;s well-known film &lt;em&gt;Inception&lt;/em&gt; has several imitations of Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Paprika&lt;/em&gt;. The scenes including elevators, corridors, etc., and even the scenes where the heroine touches the mirror in the dream are the same. There are also many classic shots in &lt;em&gt;Perfect Blue&lt;/em&gt;, which have been borrowed by many well-known directors, such as the scene where Mima is immersed in the bathtub is imitated by &lt;em&gt;Requiem for a Dream&lt;/em&gt;. The conflict between actor Mima and idol Mima is imitated by &lt;em&gt;Black Swan&lt;/em&gt;. When it came to &lt;em&gt;Millennium Actress&lt;/em&gt;, Kon Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s storytelling talent was on full display. &lt;em&gt;Millennium Actress&lt;/em&gt; not only has a lot of fanfic clips, but the heroine&amp;rsquo;s chase scene is even more beautiful. In a chase, the fast-paced editing blends the elongation of time and space, countless delicate transitions, and period drama-like silhouettes, and still can maintain the unhurried and exactly right breathing rate of the whole movie. Unfortunately, he as a dream builder can never finish his last dream before he left, the film &lt;em&gt;Dream Machine&lt;/em&gt;.  But still, his legacy of presenting dreams in such a realistic way inspired countless artists to step into the film and animation industry. His dream is unfinished, because all the artist he influenced are carrying it forward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work Cited&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aronofsky, Darren. “Black Swan.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 3 Feb. 2011, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0947798&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0947798&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aronofsky, Darren. “Requiem for a Dream.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 13 Sept. 2001, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0180093&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0180093&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro, Otomo. “Akira.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 16 July 1988, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0094625&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0094625&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro, Otomo. “Metoroporisu.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 26 May 2001, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0293416&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0293416&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro, Otomo. “Rojin Z.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 14 Sept. 1991, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0102812&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0102812&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katsuhiro, Otomo. “Steamboy.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 17 July 2004, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0348121&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0348121&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. &lt;em&gt;Kon’s Tone&lt;/em&gt;. 復刊ドットコム, 1, Jan. 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. “Memorizu.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 23 Dec. 1995, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0113799&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0113799&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. “Millennium Actress.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 14 Sept. 2002, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0291350&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0291350&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. “Paprika.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 25 Nov. 2006, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0851578/&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0851578/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. “Paranoia Agent.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 2 Feb. 2004, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0433722&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0433722&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. “Perfect Blue.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 28 Feb. 1998, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0156887&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt0156887&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kon, Satoshi. “Satoshi Kon’s Last Words.” &lt;em&gt;Makiko Itoh&lt;/em&gt;, 26 Aug. 2010, makikoitoh.com/journal/satoshi-kons-last-words.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lacan, Jacques. “Fetishism: The Symbolic, the Imaginary and the Real” (with W. Granoff), 1956. M. Balint (ed.), &lt;em&gt;Perversions: Psychodynamics and Therapy&lt;/em&gt;, New York: Random House, London: Tavistock. p. 273&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lacan, Jacques, 1901-1981. &lt;em&gt;The Seminar of Jacques Lacan&lt;/em&gt;. New York: Norton, 19882015.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loo, Egan. “Perfect Blue/Paprika Director Satoshi Kon Passes Away.” &lt;em&gt;Anime News Network&lt;/em&gt;, 24 Aug. 2010, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.animenewsnetwork.com/news/2010-08-24/award-winning-director-satoshi-kon-passes-away&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.animenewsnetwork.com/news/2010-08-24/award-winning-director-satoshi-kon-passes-away&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mary, Jacobus. “The Poetics of Psychoanalysis”, (Oxford 2005). p. 26&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nolan, Christopher. “Inception.” &lt;em&gt;IMDb&lt;/em&gt;, 16 July 2010, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1375666&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.imdb.com/title/tt1375666&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sharpe, Matthew. “Lacan, Jacques.” &lt;em&gt;Internet Encyclopedia of Philosophy&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://iep.utm.edu/lacweb/&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://iep.utm.edu/lacweb/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Aesthetic Value and Construction of the Kowloon Walled City</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/89debba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 00:19:33 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/89debba/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/research-paper/">Research Paper</category>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Laren McClung&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EXPOS-UA 5 059&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;29 Nov. 2021&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-aesthetic-value-and-construction-of-the-kowloon-walled-city&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Aesthetic Value and Construction of the Kowloon Walled City&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#the-aesthetic-value-and-construction-of-the-kowloon-walled-city&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://flashbak.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/kowloon-27.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Kowloon City&#34; srcset=&#34;https://flashbak.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/kowloon-27.jpg?size=small, https://flashbak.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/kowloon-27.jpg?size=medium 1.5x, https://flashbak.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/kowloon-27.jpg?size=large 2x&#34; data-title=&#34;Kowloon City&#34; style=&#34;background: url(/images/loading.min.svg) no-repeat center;&#34; onload=&#34;this.title=this.dataset.title;for(const i of [&#39;style&#39;, &#39;data-title&#39;,&#39;onerror&#39;,&#39;onload&#39;]){this.removeAttribute(i);}this.dataset.lazyloaded=&#39;&#39;;&#34; onerror=&#34;this.title=this.dataset.title;for(const i of [&#39;style&#39;, &#39;data-title&#39;,&#39;onerror&#39;,&#39;onload&#39;]){this.removeAttribute(i);}&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a photo of the Kowloon Walled City. The photo was taken from the outside of the walled city, a commercial street composed of buildings. In the lower part of the photo, which is the part of the commercial street accessible to pedestrians, there are many billboards written in Chinese. Below these dense billboards, there are shuttle pedestrians. It is worth noting that on the edge of the road, a large amount of rubbish is piled up disorderly and no one cleans it. In the upper part of the photo, there is a residential area made up of windowsills like cages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The whole photo has a strong taste of Hong Kong streets. And this kind of dense, even artistic architectural complex structure. This special architectural composition is one of the most artistically valuable in the Kowloon Walled City in Hong Kong. This photo was taken by Greg Girard between 1986 to 1992. He simply titled this photo gallery &lt;em&gt;Kowloon Walled City&lt;/em&gt; (Girard). Behind the photo, what he expresses is the real life of Kowloon Walled City, its special composition method and the unique history produced by history. This photo directly shows the rubbish on the ground caused by the lack of management and infrastructure construction in the Walled City, and this photo is only a corner of the exterior of the Kowloon Walled City. Inside the Kowloon Walled City, chaotic alleys, irregular three-dimensional building structures, and dark and narrow living spaces reflect the special nature of this area.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Living in the Kowloon Walled City is not something to look forward to. As Greg Girard introduced in his book &lt;em&gt;City of Darkness Revisited&lt;/em&gt;, there is a lack of drinking water supply inside the walled city, power shortage, and small living space (Girard). But what is strange is that the existence of the Kowloon Walled City and its special way of existence make artists try their best to reproduce this architectural style. As Derek Mead introduced in the article &lt;em&gt;A New Look at Kowloon Walled City, the Internet&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Cyberpunk Slum&lt;/em&gt;. The most well-known art style that represent Kowloon Walled City is Cyberpunk. And the writer who firstly introduced this type of visual impact to the public by novel is an American Sci-fi writer, William Gibson. William Gibson saw Greg Girard&amp;rsquo;s photo during his trip in Japan. This directly stimulated William Gibson&amp;rsquo;s subsequent writing. His famous work &lt;em&gt;Neuromancer&lt;/em&gt; visually reproduces the Kowloon Walled City (Mead). In the decades that followed, Kowloon Walled City became an excellent form of cyberpunk. Aside from other derivative works, just this photo of Greg Girard is enough to show the beauty of the structure of the Kowloon Walled City. Why is such a place not worth living in so attractive, so that people continue to reproduce in the works of art? What is it about the chaotic architectural complex with a very low quality of life like The Kowloon Walled City that makes it repeatedly drawn in the modern era of continuous technological and economic development? What is the aesthetic significance of Kowloon Walled City in art?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The special construction of Kowloon Walled City is a special result formed in a special historical process. The colonization of the British Empire controlled Hong Kong, which the Qing Dynasty could not govern, but the Qing government tried its best to retain the administrative power of the Kowloon area. Unfortunately, the collapse of the Qing government is already a matter of time. As Derek Mead concluded about the history of this city, next to the crumbling Qing government, Kowloon has become an extra-legal place surrounded by high walls and no one is willing to take responsibility (Mead). Due to the lack of jurisdiction, Kowloon Walled City has become an excellent place for refugees from the World War II (Mead). They finally formed a residential area spontaneously, which is also the preface for the Kowloon Walled City to grow into a complex of buildings. In other words, the aesthetic value of the Kowloon Walled City is due to its chaos and disorder. What is special about a chaotic architecture as an artwork?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the 1960s, the most glorious development of the Kowloon Walled City, the Walled City was already quite large. The population has also been increasing due to the Chinese Civil War and the Cultural Revolution (Mead). The development of the Kowloon Walled City is determined by the people who live in it. The population that settles later will live in the higher, newly built floors. In general, if the Kowloon Walled City is defined as a collection of works of art, then the residents are the artists who created the works. If you want to participate in the creation of the Kowloon Walled City, you must live in it, that is, enter the work. As critic John Berger writes, &amp;ldquo;The secret was to get inside whatever I was looking at - a bucket of water, a cow, a city (like Toledo) seen from above, an oak tree; and once inside, to arrange its appearances for the better&amp;rdquo; (Berger 30). Entering the work is to understand it better, but not to make it better in the literal sense. To be honest, the situation at the Kowloon Walled City is not optimistic. For the audience, entering the interior will not feel the beauty in the traditional sense. Entering it is to feel the good brought about by its difference. How did this paradoxical aesthetic value come about? In the definition of the aesthetic value of an artwork, its value is defined by the artist and the work, so the participation of the artist has become a part of the aesthetic value. In the process of constructing the Kowloon Walled City, what kind of relationship does the artist, or the residents, have with the work in the process of participating in the creation?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a distance between the work and the creator. This distance allows the audience to see themselves as a real audience instead of entering the work purely. This distance maintains the author&amp;rsquo;s rationality when creating, because if the author does not reserve rationality in the process of creation, the author will turn everything they have into a work. When the author becomes a work, the work cannot be separated from it. Artwork that is too close does not represent a pure form of expression but takes the author as a part of the form of expression. According to John Berger’s point of view about distance in artwork, &amp;ldquo;To go in close means forgetting convention, reputation, reasoning, hiaerarchies, and self. It also means risking incoherence, even madness. For it can happen that one gets too close and then the collaboration breaks down and the painter dissolves into the model&amp;rdquo; (Berger 30). This lack of distance is dissolve, mentioned by John Berger in his article Toward a Small Theory of the Visible. Too close distance makes the author unable to separate from the act of creation, so the author&amp;rsquo;s creation is constantly evolving itself. Because when the distance is missing, the author is trying their best to express themselves, rather than expressing only as a form of art. In this evolution of the self, the creator constantly discovers and denies the part of consciousness that denies the self, and the creation is not the evolution of something. But in this process, negation keeps appearing. Therefore, this continuous cycle allows the creator to dissolve into their own evolution, that is, evolution loses the distance from the self. And this continuous evolution loses continuity at the same time, because in the process of constant negation, the process of evolution is out of self-coordination. Therefore, in this incoherent cycle of negation, the ego has fallen into madness. Because even though we are constantly negating evolution, this evolution has never touched the self that expresses self-approval. Therefore, in order to express this self-extracted self, the creator must enter a hysterical cycle. Constantly denying evolution in an incoherent cycle, creating madness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike an ordinary city, where residents do not participate in the design and construction of houses. Even if they participate, they are not really taking over with full authority, but just choose what meets their own wishes from some of the presets given by others. This creation is a kind of cooperation, a two-way cater to the art form and the creator&amp;rsquo;s wishes. This kind of cooperation liberates the creator from conflict, because there is no conflict between the work and the creator. This is the distance of creation. This distance brings a sense of security to the creator and to the residents who are also viewers. In the Kowloon Walled City, residents are creators and audiences at the same time. However, because the creators live directly in the work, the disappearance of this distance directly leads to the residents of Kowloon Walled City who project their entire self completely when they are creating their own houses. Because the distance of creation disappears, the work becomes an evolution of the self. Therefore, the residents carry out house construction in the negation of the cycle. Specifically, the houses in the Kowloon Walled City are not like ordinary cities that are contracted and constructed by developers. On the contrary, it is formed by an anarchistic self-evolution. That is, a new building is superimposed on the completed building again. This is the negation of fixed construction. Because even the completed buildings will evolve because of housing needs, which will negate themselves. In this process of evolution, negation did not disappear, but was covered by the process of evolution. Strictly speaking, it should be kept under the evolution. Residents participate in this evolution, not only the builders of the evolution, but also the demanders and appreciators. Moreover, the evolution of this cycle is not carried out by a specific individual but constructed by a group. In other words, to use this to explain the relationship between artists and architecture in the Kowloon Walled City is a construction that is the negation of the cycle of group consciousness. In the process of this construction, the building continues to evolve, making the building itself the basis of architectural evolution. In the Kowloon Walled City, one of the most prominent photos of this evolution is an indoor temple. A very small temple runs through the first and second floors, and above the temple is a semi-transparent floor similar to a barbed wire. This barbed wire became the floor of the floor above the temple. This kind of wonderful conflict is a challenge to traditional architectural aesthetics. This challenge is initiated by denial and evolution. Because it is the evolution that takes place above the negation that the inhabitants as artists can withdraw their self-completed self and create madness from this incoherent evolution. It is this challenge that has become a major feature of the Kowloon Walled City architecture, that is, its architectural aesthetics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After dissolving the traditional artistic creation relationship, the creation process of Kowloon Walled City became the fundamental reason for its unique architectural aesthetics. This crazy evolution challenges traditional architectural relationships. Because this challenge is not a pure, detached art. It is attached to an entire operational building system. Just like Terry Tempest Williams’ definition of the nature of art, “Art is dangerous because it doesn’t have a definable function. I think that is what people are afraid of” (Williams 43). In Williams’ understanding, art is dangerous. Because it has no specific definable function. But the Kowloon Walled City directly challenged this view, because the existence of the Walled City itself exists for the purpose of living. The reason why Kowloon Walled City has its special architectural aesthetic value is that its entire artistic relationship and architectural model challenge traditional artistic methods. But this does not mean that the Kowloon Walled City is not dangerous. On the contrary, it is precisely because it does its best to challenge traditional art that it is even more dangerous. Because the author has fallen into the artwork of the Walled City, after throwing away the value of residence, it becomes a purely dangerous artwork. It is precisely because the Kowloon Walled City regards chaos and disorder as the core of its aesthetics, and this chaos and disorder is at the same time the most meaningless function, the walled city as a work of art is even more dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The chaos and disorder of the Kowloon Walled City arise from its special historical background, and this special history has led to its special architectural model. At too close a distance, crazy challenges were continuously launched. And such a challenge puts the walled city in the position of the most dangerous artwork. This is the reason for its charm, and this is the most aesthetic aspect of the entire area as a building. Its special mode of existence challenges people&amp;rsquo;s cognition of artworks, and at the same time makes people shudder-what a dangerous and beautiful place. It is all this that puts the artistry of Kowloon Walled City to a terrifying height. That is the reason why people continue to reproduce it-people have discovered the hidden dangers in this strange chaotic pattern, and they want to do their best to discover the aesthetic value of dangerous works of art. This is what makes the Kowloon Walled City secure an important position in the history of art, and makes artists continue to challenge this unique artistic beauty.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work Cited&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Girard, Greg. &lt;em&gt;City Of Darkness: Revisited&lt;/em&gt;. Edited by Ian Lambot Ed., Watermark, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;John, Berger. &lt;em&gt;John Berger Steps Towards a Small Theory of the Visible /Anglais (GREAT IDEAS)&lt;/em&gt;. PENGUIN UK, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mead, Derek. “A New Look at Kowloon Walled City, the Internet’s Favorite Cyberpunk Slum.” &lt;em&gt;VICE&lt;/em&gt;, 3 Apr. 2014, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vice.com/en/article/kbzwvm/a-new-look-at-kowloon-walled-city-the-internets-favorite-cyberpunk-slum&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.vice.com/en/article/kbzwvm/a-new-look-at-kowloon-walled-city-the-internets-favorite-cyberpunk-slum&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Williams, Terry. “A Shark in the Mind of One Contemplating Wilderness&amp;quot;.” &lt;em&gt;The Nation&lt;/em&gt;, Nov. 1999, pp. 42–44.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumerism In Advertisement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/42936c4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 23:38:30 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/42936c4/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/research-paper/">Research Paper</category>
      <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Daniel Johnson&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EAST-UA 950 002&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;13 Dec. 2021&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;consumerism-in-advertisement&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Consumerism In Advertisement&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#consumerism-in-advertisement&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After World War II, with the economic recovery and prosperity, consumption gradually replaced production and became the core of urban residents&amp;rsquo; lives. Western developed countries led by the United States began to enter the consumer society one after another. In Asia, Japan has gone through the most prosperous 1980s in its reflections on wars. At the same time, both South Korea and China have entered a stage of rapid economic development. At this stage, the fatal crisis of capitalism in the era of heavy industry and colonialism was hidden by the economic climax, while at the same time it was exploiting the humanity more covertly. From the post-war era until the arrival of the 21st century, consumer capitalism has always been hidden under the beauty of economic development, affecting the daily lives of Asian people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consumerism, in essence, is a powerful variant of capitalism and a manifestation of capitalism-it promises all happiness and beauty in the form of fetishism to maintain and suppress the inherent contradictions and crises of capitalism. The consumer society is destined to be the best habitat for advertising. One of the main characteristics of the consumer era is ubiquitous advertising. And one of the essences of advertising is consumerism, which is to encourage consumption, stimulate consumption, and lead and even create consumer demand. Consumerism in Asia in the 1980s took a ride on technological development. In the context of the technological explosion, the spread of symbols depends on emerging media. Advertisements are spread more widely through emerging technologies such as VRC, radio, and television.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The distinguishing feature of the era of mass culture is the dramatic increase in symbols. Especially the dramatic increase in image symbols, and &amp;ldquo;visualization&amp;rdquo; has been placed in a prominent position. We live in a symbolic empire. The statement that advertising is the &amp;ldquo;king&amp;rdquo; of this symbolic empire is a bit exaggerated, but it does not falsely show the prominent position of advertising in the current society. The current society is that advertising is everywhere, where &amp;ldquo;encountering&amp;rdquo; various advertisements is one of the daily experiences that modern people are familiar with. The American communication professor Sut Jhally described in his book &lt;em&gt;Image-Based Culture&lt;/em&gt; the current situation of society being filled with information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In the contemporary world, messages about goods are all pervasive-advertising has increasingly filled up the spaces of our daily existence. Our media are dominated by advertising images, public space has been taken over by ‘information’ about products, and most of our sporting and cultural events are accompanied by the name of a corporate sponsor” (Jhally 200).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world he described, advertisements are flooded within people’s symbol systems. Sut Jhally explained the process of using symbols to represent products to engage the media then output into information. The symbolic language of daily life is squeezed by advertisements. In this squeezing process, advertising sells not only products but also a consumer social order that is universally involved and cannot be circumvented or not allowed to be circumvented. Because advertising cannot be avoided. Advertising manages the needs of consumers. It teaches people what to expect from consuming every item. In other words, it tells people what each object gives them, or an object gives them what kind of results will it bring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Andrew C. McKevitt is introducing Sony&amp;rsquo;s attempt to promote Betamax in 1985. Betamax is a VCR that can record video on tape in a portable way. “A brief paragraph beneath the image explained in simple language just what the Betamax did—what, when, how, and how long it recorded. The ads finished by evoking the image of empowerment: ‘You’re always stuck watching what the networks want Why not watch what you want instead&amp;rsquo;” (McKevitt 138)? In the example given by Andrew C. McKevitt, Sony directly gave consumers the reason to buy Betamax: “You want it”. Sony created a demand order in the process of this advertisement, that is, people need a video recorder. Sony promotes Betamax by creating demand for consumers. It is undeniable that VCR had a positive impact on the Japanese cultural industry in the 1980s, but the positive potential of the product is amplified in publicity and is also a part of advertising. Sut Jhally pointed out that because advertising is to achieve a positive publicity purpose, then it must show the positive side of the product. But this positivity is usually not directly related to the product.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If goods themselves are not the locus of perceived happiness, then they need to be connected in some way with those things that are. Thus advertising promotes images of what the audience conceives of as &amp;ldquo;the good life&amp;rdquo;: Beer can be connected with anything from eroticism to male fraternity to the purity of the old West; food can be tied up with family relations or health; investment advice offers early retirements in tropical settings. The marketplace cannot directly offer the real thing, but it can offer visions of it connected with the purchase of products” (Jhally 201).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The advertisement itself does not have a positive meaning, but the promotion adds a positive necessity to the product. What advertising appeals to is not the core of modernity—the spirit of rationality—but the core of postmodernity, that is, the commercial construction of an anti-rational spirit for infinite interpretation and generation of infinite meaning. Therefore, as a symbol, the advertisement itself is separated from the product itself in everything that is laid to promote the enthusiasm of the product. As a result, more and more advertisements have gradually become irrelevant to the details of the product itself and are devoted to the emotional clues that are irrelevant. Through the misappropriation of cultural resources and the mechanism of discourse conversion, savvy advertising makers can hide the consumerist nature of advertisements just right, and replace them with a non-commercial, non-utilitarian face—or tenderness, or following good temptations, or respectful teaching—that will give the audience a series of illusions, as if they are seeing scenes of family dramas, charity films, or science and education films, but they have nothing to do with consumption. Therefore, this society has moved from &amp;ldquo;function&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;entity&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;symbol&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;simulacrum&amp;rdquo;. Only signs and simulacra can transcend the real world and create endless illusions of a better life for capital.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Japan in the 1980s and 1990s was the era when consumerism prevailed. Before the Plaza Accord, the Japanese economy had been in a booming bubble. This prosperity also brought soil for the spread of consumerism. Coca-Cola used &amp;ldquo;I Feel Coke&amp;rdquo; as a slogan in TV commercials produced for Japan in the 1980s. In the 1987 &amp;ldquo;I Feel Coke&amp;rdquo; TV commercial, Coca-Cola filmed many scenes where young people were very happy with Coca-Cola in their hands. This montage technique connects Coca-Cola with happy, energetic youth. From a semiotic point of view, in the visual expression of advertising, signifier, every scene is full of strong &amp;ldquo;voiceover&amp;rdquo;, signified. This advertisement brings the audience into the setting scene by reproducing various desirable happiness scenes in real life. The purpose of Coca-Cola is to make consumers think that Coca-Cola is the cause of their happiness in this connection, and this is a fashion trend. So, advertising doesn’t just encourage people to buy products. It also brings people to a world where they learn how to connect special things with special social concepts and meanings. Therefore, even if advertising cannot persuade people to buy a particular product, it is still a winner, because its main goal is to force society to accept the meaning of the advertising language or object and its relationship with people’s lives. In short, the main purpose of advertising is to make people believe in and obey the rules that it bestows on people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jean Baudrillard is one of the most important social scientists and philosophers in France in the 20th century. Because of the importance of advertising in consumer culture, his book &lt;em&gt;The System of Objects&lt;/em&gt; repeatedly mentioned the operating logic of advertising as a symbolic communication medium. &amp;ldquo;The entire modern environment is thus transposed onto the level of a sign system, namely ATOMOSPHERE, which is no lover produced by the way any particular element is handled, nor by the beauty or ugliness of that element&amp;rdquo; (Baudrillard 40). Jean Baudrillard found that in today&amp;rsquo;s society, signs are gradually decoupled from the signifier that refers to signs. As a medium for propagating goods, advertisements are becoming more and more detached from the goods themselves. Advertising is not just an appendage of the object system. Because the role of advertising is never strictly to provide information. Advertising as a whole creates a useless and unnecessary universe. It is a pure, woven &amp;ldquo;meaning&amp;rdquo;. Advertising has no contribution to the production or the direct practical application of things, but it plays an inseparable role in the object system, not only because it is related to consumption, but also because it itself has become an object of consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Penguin&amp;rsquo;s Memory: Shiawase Monogatari&lt;/em&gt; is a 1985 Japanese animation film. This movie uses the image of a cartoon penguin to tell a cruel story about war and love. The male protagonist Mike and the female protagonist Jill experience love in the trauma of the post-war period. But instead of treating this movie as a pure movie, it is more of a promotion for a beverage brand. Suntory Beer first printed the images of these two cartoon penguins on beer cans in 1983. This kind of publicity not only links the image of Penguin to the taste of beer but also makes Penguin itself a brand. At the moment the penguin is born, the penguin can survive without beer. Because the penguin does not contain any information about the beer itself, nor does it exist depending on the beer. This pure, woven penguin is an objects to be consumed independent of beer. Penguins were born to promote beer, and in the end, they themselves became the objects to be consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;American philosopher Fredric Jameson pointed out in his article &lt;em&gt;Postmodernism, or, The Cultural Logic of Late Capitalism&lt;/em&gt; that contemporary society is gradually disintegrating the meaning of signs. The existence of meaninglessness itself is replacing the meaning of signs. &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; in a cultural form of image addiction which, by transforming the past visual mirages, stereotypes or texts, effectively abolishes any practical sense of the future and of the collective project, thereby abandoning the thinking of future change to fantasies of sheer catastrophe and inexplicable cataclysm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; (Jameson &amp;ldquo;Postmodernism&amp;rdquo; VI). The deconstruction of meanings is the projection of postmodern society. In modern society, advertising is responsible for promoting consumption. While in postmodern society, advertising itself is the objects to be consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A very representative postmodern derivative work is &lt;em&gt;“M.C.ドナルドはダンスに夢中なのか？最終鬼畜道化師ドナルド・Ｍ”&lt;/em&gt; published on the Niconico website in 2008. This is a spoof of Ronald McDonald&amp;rsquo;s video, which shows an absurd look and feel by adding background music and creating a &amp;ldquo;twitch&amp;rdquo; picture. The original video is a McDonald’s advertisement in Japan between 2004 and 2007. Ronald McDonald&amp;rsquo;s own image is actually the same as Suntory Beer&amp;rsquo;s penguin. Their existence has nothing to do with the product itself. Although the derivative work that has received much attention spreads the existence of Ronald McDonald on a meaningless level, it does not tell the audience what McDonald&amp;rsquo;s sells. This lack of meaning makes the existence of the advertising image itself added &amp;ldquo;meaning&amp;rdquo;. The derivative work directly expresses how the advertisement itself is used as an object to be consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The advertising system creates a hierarchy of status and prestige and forces us to accept them. Every commodity is a symbol, which has a special meaning and status in this system. It can position a person with a special power and status. The idol industry in Japan has continued to develop since the end of the war. The idol industry eventually gradually broke away from the artists, or idols themselves, under the influence of the capitalist trend. In the end, the idol industry completely transformed people into products, and in the process of this change, idols themselves also played a role as an advertisement. As described by Jimmie L. Reeves, idols are like advertisements which &amp;ldquo;contributes to the production, maintenance, repair and transformation of social reality by animating aritual of social typification and individualization&amp;rdquo; (qtd. in Stevens and Hosokawa 241). In the second half of the 20th century in Japan, idols were produced more in the music industry. The TV companies discovered a business opportunity to build singers into products to make money. By gathering singers and holding TV events, they created fan circles centered on singers or groups. This kind of fan circle is usually exclusive and uses music taste as the criterion for distinguishing among them. When the audiences are not just listeners of music, but supporters of the singers, the mentality of the audience are not just a bystander. The popularity of their singers can be regarded as a representative of their musical taste in their eyes. Therefore, this kind of exclusive fan structure usually requires a common sense of identity, that is, to position themselves in a higher taste through consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the article &lt;em&gt;So Close and yet So Far&lt;/em&gt; by Carolyn S. Stevens and Shuhei Hosokawa, they found that as early as the 60s TV show The Best Ten, they had already added a ranking to the singer&amp;rsquo;s program and used real-time updates to consume the audience&amp;rsquo;s fetish of idol (Stevens and Hosokawa 229). They analyzed the role of music rankings in the idol industry. &amp;ldquo;The rankings, which tell audiences what is&amp;rsquo; hot&amp;rsquo;, act as a tool to produce a feeling of shared taste&amp;rdquo; (Stevens and Hosokawa 233). In this standard, The sales ranking of songs shaped by TV companies through programs has become a model for fans to judge their music tastes. By using musicians as products, a hierarchy is established among their respective consumer segments. In this model, idols serve as both an advertisement and a product. As a result, the audiences are forced to squeeze each other into the system created by idols. Idols, as artists, were squeezed out of creative freedom (Stevens and Hosokawa 229), in order to create economic benefits for the company. While the audiences were squeezed into sales for idols in order to satisfy the model of desire of their own musical tastes. In this process of squeezing, both parts contributed surplus value to the expansion of consumerism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Karl Marx, under capitalism, the ruling class and the owners try to create new &amp;ldquo;demands&amp;rdquo; on people and try to alienate traditional needs and even give them a capital value. In a capitalist society, the biggest problem for workers is not only the exploitation of economic interests and surplus-value but more importantly, they are alienated and separated from their true interests and their own creations. They work only to create economic benefits without creating any sense of spiritual accomplishment and the positive externalities of altruism (Marx &amp;ldquo;Comment on James Mill&amp;rdquo;). This is capitalism&amp;rsquo;s alienation of people. In a society where traditional semiotic meanings are all deconstructed by postmodern consumerism, advertisements composed of pure meanings forcefully induce and call viewers to identify with the product, thus becoming a consumer. Therefore, people’s desires in a consumerist society are created, as Stijn Vanheule explained in his article &lt;em&gt;Capitalist Discourse, Subjectivity and Lacanian Psychoanalysis&lt;/em&gt;: “Marcuse (1964) suggests that capitalism integrates people in a model of consumerism, where they work and consume more than they need. This not only has damaging effects on the environment and on social life but also contaminates mental life by installing false needs that people want to satisfy&amp;rdquo; (Vanheule). They lost their universality in the commodity fetishes that were released, and gradually alienated them into inhumanity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work Cited&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#work-cited&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baudrillard, Jean. &lt;em&gt;The System of Objects (Latin American and Iberian Studies Series)&lt;/em&gt;. Verso, 1996.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jameson, Fredric. “Postmodernism, or The Cultural Logic of Late Capitalism.” &lt;em&gt;New Left Review&lt;/em&gt;, 1 Aug. 1984, newleftreview.org/issues/i146/articles/fredric-jameson-postmodernism-or-the-cultural-logic-of-late-capitalism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jhally, Sut. &lt;em&gt;Image-Based Culture Advertising and Popular Culture&lt;/em&gt;. The World and I, 1990.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kimura, Shinji, director. &lt;em&gt;Penguin&amp;rsquo;s Memory - Shiawase Monogatari&lt;/em&gt;. 1985.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Marx, Karl. &amp;ldquo;Comment on James Mill.&amp;rdquo; Economic and Philosophical Manuscripts of 1844, 1844.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;McKevitt, Andrew. “A Medium but Not a Message: The VCR and Cultural Globalization.” &lt;em&gt;Consuming Japan: Popular Culture and the Globalizing of 1980s America (Studies in United States Culture)&lt;/em&gt;, Illustrated, University of North Carolina Press, 2017, pp. 131–53.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stevens, Carolyn, and Shūhei Hosokawa. &lt;em&gt;So Close and Yet So Far: Humanizing Celebrity in Japanese Music Variety Shows, 1960s-1990s&lt;/em&gt;. 2001.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vanheule, Stijn. “Capitalist Discourse, Subjectivity and Lacanian Psychoanalysis.” &lt;em&gt;Frontiers&lt;/em&gt;, 2016, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2016.01948/full#B15&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2016.01948/full#B15&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;みくる さん. “M.C.ドナルドはダンスに夢中なのか？最終鬼畜道化師ドナルド・Ｍ.” ニコニコ動画, 16 Jan. 2008, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm2057168&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;www.nicovideo.jp/watch/sm2057168&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booklist</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/c8e0ceb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:20:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/c8e0ceb/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/draft/">Draft</category>
      <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
