<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rhetoric - Tag - Shannon&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/rhetoric/</link>
    <description>Shannon&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.136.4 &amp; FixIt v0.3.13</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:40:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/rhetoric/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Phaedrus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a0f523b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:40:10 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a0f523b/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Plato. &lt;em&gt;Plato: Complete Works&lt;/em&gt;. Hackett Publishing, 1997. &lt;em&gt;Phaedrus&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On my first day of seventh grade (freshman year of junior high school), I had a very childish argument with a kid wearing glasses about a stupid question. The main form of this argument was as follows:&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;re stupid.&#xA;Bounce back!&#xA;Bounce is not valid!&#xA;The rebound is valid, period!&#xA;My IQ is twice yours, comma!&#xA;My IQ is your absolute value!&#xA;Of course, we could go on and on with this rhetorical question. However, when I first heard the concept of &amp;ldquo;absolute value,&amp;rdquo; I realized I couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue the argument. The reason was that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what &amp;ldquo;absolute value&amp;rdquo; was, i.e., I had no signified in my head, and my whole language system went down for a few seconds. Perhaps in retrospect, we could have stacked that argument with concepts like &amp;ldquo;squaring,&amp;rdquo; but that would have implied some kind of rhetorical rift.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do You All Think?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/36d01d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:01:29 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/36d01d8/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a speech I made for the class Classical Literature &amp;amp; Philosophy with prof. Emanuela Bianchi.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the first class, our professor wrote guidelines for our oral presentation and told us that we need to kick off the class discussion with a thought-provoking question at the end, but to avoid overly broad questions such as &amp;ldquo;So what do you all think? I then wondered if the question was really that broad. But I finally decided to use this question as the centerpiece of the discussion, and my presentation would inevitably end the class discussion with this question. Even if my motivation at the outset was resistance to the father&amp;rsquo;s injunctions - anti-Oedipus on a Freudian level.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
