<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prose - Category - Holzwage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/</link>
    <description>Holzwage</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.136.4 &amp; FixIt v0.3.13</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:57:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Orientalism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/d10832d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:57:16 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/d10832d/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aeschylus. &lt;em&gt;The Persians&lt;/em&gt;. Prentice Hall, 1970.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gruen, Erich S. “Rethinking the Other in Antiquity.” &lt;em&gt;Princeton University Press eBooks&lt;/em&gt;, 2010, &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1515/9781400836550&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;external nofollow noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1515/9781400836550&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Said, Edward W. &lt;em&gt;Orientalism: Western Conceptions of the Orient&lt;/em&gt;. Penguin UK, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like to combine this week&amp;rsquo;s reading and the important psychoanalytic theory of the Other with the basic position I stated last week. Sans the tedious theoretical elaboration of the Mirror Stage, the conclusion is simple: one subject can only see himself from the Others&amp;rsquo; eyes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Feminism, A Hysterical Writing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/9ac6a2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:47:41 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/9ac6a2d/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Irigaray, Luce. &lt;em&gt;Sexes and Genealogies&lt;/em&gt;. 1993. pg9-21.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Very interesting article. The very act of the author questioning the legality of phallus is an act of patricide. The topic of contraception and abortion was a highly controversial subject in the United States of America in the 1980&amp;rsquo;s and to this day. In China, however, abortion has not been a taboo since ancient times. The Han Book, written in 105 A.D., records the use of medication for abortion by the ancient Chinese.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phaedrus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a0f523b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:40:10 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a0f523b/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Plato. &lt;em&gt;Plato: Complete Works&lt;/em&gt;. Hackett Publishing, 1997. &lt;em&gt;Phaedrus&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On my first day of seventh grade (freshman year of junior high school), I had a very childish argument with a kid wearing glasses about a stupid question. The main form of this argument was as follows:&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;re stupid.&#xA;Bounce back!&#xA;Bounce is not valid!&#xA;The rebound is valid, period!&#xA;My IQ is twice yours, comma!&#xA;My IQ is your absolute value!&#xA;Of course, we could go on and on with this rhetorical question. However, when I first heard the concept of &amp;ldquo;absolute value,&amp;rdquo; I realized I couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue the argument. The reason was that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what &amp;ldquo;absolute value&amp;rdquo; was, i.e., I had no signified in my head, and my whole language system went down for a few seconds. Perhaps in retrospect, we could have stacked that argument with concepts like &amp;ldquo;squaring,&amp;rdquo; but that would have implied some kind of rhetorical rift.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oedipus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/7fcc04f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 17:33:10 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/7fcc04f/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Sophocles&amp;rsquo; stories, God is always an extremely important object. He always appears as an inviolable figure. In the story of Oedipus, no matter how hard Oedipus and his own parents try, the prophecies of the gods are always fulfilled. This great burden is present in the form of fate.&#xA;Oedipus comes to Tiresias to explain who is the contamination, and because Tiresias points out that Oedipus is the contamination, the two begin to quarrel over who is the &amp;ldquo;blind&amp;rdquo; (370-410). This reminds me of Lacan&amp;rsquo;s reference in a seminar of The Purloined Letter to three different kinds of people: &amp;ldquo;blind, seer and robber&amp;rdquo;; blind does not see, seer knows that blind does not see and pretends not to see, and robber sees what lies beneath the surface. Blind can&amp;rsquo;t see, seer knows blind can&amp;rsquo;t see and pretends he can&amp;rsquo;t see, and robber sees what lies beneath the surface.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love to Sophia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/6750eef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 17:28:11 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/6750eef/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Curd, Patricia. &lt;em&gt;A Presocratics Reader: Selected Fragments and Testimonia&lt;/em&gt;. Hackett Publishing, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Astrology had a very important place in the theoretical system of these ancient philosophers. Their philosophical ideas, however, were in a state of infantile speculation about natural phenomena during the period of human civilization&amp;rsquo;s exploration of the unknown. Although it is said that the three Milesians were wrong about the world because basic chemistry and physics were not developed at that time, and even mathematics was in an embryonic stage. But that does not mean that there is nothing to learn from their ideas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antigone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/9fbbf41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 17:19:31 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/9fbbf41/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A story like this can be understood in many ways. It can be a conflict between natural law and man-made law, or a conflict between a positivist position and a non-positivist position on the same legal case. Antigone, in jurisprudential terms, stands for natural law, and Creon stands for man-made law. It seems that the story simply discusses the importance of natural law (morality). It seems to be a confrontation between morality and law. But Antigone&amp;rsquo;s story has a certain sublime value in it. The characters in the story have a very unusual emphasis on the definition of womanhood.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do You All Think?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/36d01d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:01:29 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/36d01d8/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a speech I made for the class Classical Literature &amp;amp; Philosophy with prof. Emanuela Bianchi.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the first class, our professor wrote guidelines for our oral presentation and told us that we need to kick off the class discussion with a thought-provoking question at the end, but to avoid overly broad questions such as &amp;ldquo;So what do you all think? I then wondered if the question was really that broad. But I finally decided to use this question as the centerpiece of the discussion, and my presentation would inevitably end the class discussion with this question. Even if my motivation at the outset was resistance to the father&amp;rsquo;s injunctions - anti-Oedipus on a Freudian level.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Color Of The World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/0e4eb88/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 01:54:15 -0400</pubDate><author>zl4061@nyu.edu (Shannon Li)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/0e4eb88/</guid>
      <category domain="http://localhost:1313/categories/prose/">Prose</category>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shannon Li&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;April. 24th, 2023&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-the-color-of-the-world&#34; class=&#34;heading-element&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;On the Color of the World&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#on-the-color-of-the-world&#34; class=&#34;heading-mark&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;svg class=&#34;octicon octicon-link&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 16 16&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; width=&#34;16&#34; height=&#34;16&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;m7.775 3.275 1.25-1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1 4.95 4.95l-2.5 2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1-4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1 .018-1.042.751.751 0 0 1 1.042-.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l2.5-2.5a2.002 2.002 0 0 0-2.83-2.83l-1.25 1.25a.751.751 0 0 1-1.042-.018.751.751 0 0 1-.018-1.042Zm-4.69 9.64a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 2.83 0l1.25-1.25a.751.751 0 0 1 1.042.018.751.751 0 0 1 .018 1.042l-1.25 1.25a3.5 3.5 0 1 1-4.95-4.95l2.5-2.5a3.5 3.5 0 0 1 4.95 0 .751.751 0 0 1-.018 1.042.751.751 0 0 1-1.042.018 1.998 1.998 0 0 0-2.83 0l-2.5 2.5a1.998 1.998 0 0 0 0 2.83Z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think, in many cases, that color is always so confusing. If it is because of personal experiences and other reasons that I choose to accept certain ideas and reject certain things. Then me, I&amp;rsquo;m always in denial. From the time I started making choices, I refused to accept them, but I was never able to reject the act of choosing itself. I could see my refusal quite clearly, but I was also refusing to accept my own disgusting refusal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
